NYSUT 'Teachers United: The Rise of NYSUT.' Research Notes. 6174/012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Research & Educational Services: Resource Guide (April 2005) -- pulled from box 3/ff60 (Box 4)
  - Research & Educational Services: Research Guide (April 2005) (Box 4, Folder 1)
    pulled from box 3/ff60